itutozone.com 2015-05-04

# Privacy Policy - Tutorial Zone

Please read the following carefully. If you have any questions or concerns, please send us an email at [info@vectordesign.com ](http://tutozone.net/file/mailto:info@vectordesign.com).

###  Gathering and Use of Information

Freevectordesign : Freevectordesign will never willfully disclose any personally identifiable information about our online audience to any third-party without first receiving the user’s permission. We do not collect personally identifiable information from our visitors other than what is supplied to us on a voluntary basis.

Visitors to the Freevectordesign : Freevectordesign may voluntarily supply certain personally identifiable information in connection with (i)contest or sweepstakes registration, (ii) subscription registration for sites or services which require subscription (such as email newsletters), (iii) requests for membership information and (iv) e-commerce transactions. In addition, personally identifiable information is voluntarily provided in connection with certain content submissions, community postings (i.e., forums or bulletin boards), comments and suggestions, or voting.

Some of our sites contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different from ours. Visitors should consult the other sites’ privacy notices as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.

Freevectordesign : Freevectordesign may use such information only for conducting the activities stated above, for internal marketing and promotional purposes, or, on occasion, when mailing lists are made available to other organizations. (The occasional provision of mailing lists to such organizations is the only case where such information would be provided to third parties).

For more information regarding Freevectordesign : Freevectordesign’s policies on the handling and use of Freevectordesign : Daily Design Inspiration’s membership list, please see Freevectordesign : Daily Design Inspiration’s Membership List Policy. The extent of such use is always explained at the time a site visitor provides such information.

If the visitor does not want this information collected and used by us for the disclosed internal purposes, the visitor is given an opportunity to ‘opt-out.’ Our visitors need to recognize, however, that under certain circumstances, if they select to ‘opt-out’ they may not be eligible for certain activities for which the personally identifiable information is needed. (For example, if a contest participant elects to ‘opt-out’ on permitting us to collect and use their personal information, we cannot contact them if they win without using such information.)

###  Acceptance of these Freevectordesign : Freevectordesign Privacy Policy Terms and Conditions

By using this site, you signify your agreement to the terms and conditions of this Freevectordesign : Daily Design Inspiration Web Site Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to these terms and conditions, please do not use the site. We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this policy at any time.

From time to time, Freevectordesign :Freevectordesign may update this privacy notice. We will notify you about material changes in the way we treat personally identifiable information by placing a notice on our site. We encourage you to periodically check back and review this policy so that you always will know what information we collect, how we use it, and to whom we disclose it. Your continued use of the Freevectordesign : Daily Design Inspiration Web Site following the posting of any changes to these terms shall mean that you have accepted those changes.

### 

We respect Google Adesense Policies

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please email us at [info@vectordesign.com](mailto:info@vectordesign.com) .
